<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Gears xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Gear>
    <Key>JT12JP</Key>
    <Name>JT-12C Jetpack</Name>
    <Description>[H3]JT-12C Jetpack[h3]
hen clone troopers need to quickly deploy in the held, they are often equipped With the JT- I QC jetpack Merr-Sonn manufactures this modified version of the JT- 1 2 for the Grand Army of the Republic. In addition to having Increased production, this variant is modified to Improve reliability for extended battlefield use. Intakes. turbines. and nozzles are hardened to reduce the need for field service. The modifications result in a slightly bulkier package. Consequently. soldiers may discard assigned units once they have  depleted their fuel cells, to reduce their encumbrance on the battlefield.[P]
A JT-2C jetpack allows a person to function as a silhouette 1 , speed 2, handling 0, system strain threshold 4 vehicle that can only operate in atmosphere and requires Piloting (Planetary) to operate.
</Description>
    <Source Page="58">Collapse of the Republic</Source>
    <Custom>AddedItem</Custom>
    <Type>Tools/Electronics</Type>
    <Categories />
    <Encumbrance>2</Encumbrance>
    <Price>4750</Price>
    <Rarity>7</Rarity>
  </Gear>
  <Gear>
    <Key>Z6JPCK</Key>
    <Name>Z-6 Jetpack</Name>
    <Description>[H3]Z-6 Jetpack[h3]
When a soldier needs to make a swift and unexpected arrival, a jetpack provides one of the quickest and most surprising methods. The pack's small thrusters enable  the wearer to blast into the air for a short time, achieving a vertical height of up to 70 meters. The pack uses a combination of verbal and wrist-mounted controls.[P]
The Z-6 provides additional tactical flexibility by incorporating a mount point for a single rocket-fired missile. Different payloads can be incorporated based upon the needs of each objective. Mitrinomon Transports manufactures the Z-6, which—alongside the JT-12—is popular among traditionally minded Mandalorians who prize the additional combat option,
 
[P]A jetpack allows a person to function as a silhouette l . speed 2, handling 0, system strain threshold 3 vehicle that can only operate in atmosphere and requires Piloting (Planetary) to operate.[P]
A Z-6 jetpack features an integrated missile launcher with the following profile: (Ranged [Heavyl; Damage 1 5; Critical 3; Range [Long); Blast 10, Breach l , Inaccurate l , Limited Ammo l , Prepare l ) .
</Description>
    <Source Page="58">Collapse of the Republic</Source>
    <Custom>AddedItem</Custom>
    <Type>Tools/Electronics</Type>
    <Categories>
      <Category />
    </Categories>
    <Encumbrance>3</Encumbrance>
    <Price>5250</Price>
    <Rarity>7</Rarity>
    <WeaponModifiers>
      <WeaponModifier>
        <UnarmedName>Integrated Rocket Launcher</UnarmedName>
        <SkillKey>RANGHVY</SkillKey>
        <Damage>15</Damage>
        <Crit>3</Crit>
        <Qualities>
          <Quality>
            <Key>BLAST</Key>
            <Count>10</Count>
          </Quality>
          <Quality>
            <Key>BREACH</Key>
            <Count>1</Count>
          </Quality>
          <Quality>
            <Key>INACCURATE</Key>
            <Count>1</Count>
          </Quality>
          <Quality>
            <Key>LIMITEDAMMO</Key>
            <Count>1</Count>
          </Quality>
          <Quality>
            <Key>PREPARE</Key>
            <Count>1</Count>
          </Quality>
        </Qualities>
        <RangeValue>wrLong</RangeValue>
        <Range>Long</Range>
      </WeaponModifier>
    </WeaponModifiers>
  </Gear>
</Gears>